Remove Watermark Nov

Lim Tze May

Address : Blk 2B, Upper Boon Keng Road, Kallang, Singapore 382002

Email : tzemay_90@hotmail.com

Contact : +65 83165831

INTRODUCTION

I have over three years of external audit experience and have spent the last two years specialising in the Funds and Capital Markets industry with RSM Chio Lim LLP, the largest audit firm outside the Big 4 in Singapore. In addition to the local statutory financial audits, I have led regulatory compliance audits of Monetary Authority of Singapore (MAS) registered fund management companies and assisted in SGX listed companies and REIT audit .

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

RSM Chio Lim LLP – Senior, Audit (2 years, October 2015 - Present)

I joined the Fund and Capital Markets team as an Audit Associate in Jan 2015 and was promoted to Audit Senior in October 2015. In October 2016, I was promoted to my current position as second year Audit Senior.

Audit Senior

- Lead Auditor-In-Charge for a SGX listed REIT with assets larger than S\$1 billion.
- Led compliance and financial team audit engagements for Fund Management Companies regulated by the MAS – Licensed Fund Management Companies ("LFMC") and Registered Fund Management Companies ("RFMC").
- Led financial audits for Singapore branch's administrative office of China's State Administration of Foreign Exchange.

Audit Associate

- Assisted in the financial audits for a variety of Singapore and Cayman Islands-registered funds, in market segments such as mutual trust, private equity, quoted & unquoted financial instruments, and distressed debt.
- Assisted in the audits for SGX listed company (nature: commodities) and SGX listed Real Estate Investment Trust (REIT).

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE (CONT'D)

RSM Chio Lim LLP – Senior, Audit (2 years, October 2015 - Present)

Audit Associate (cont'd)

- Assisted in Group's audits.
- Led in local statutory audits.

Pricewaterhouse Coopers, Malaysia – Audit Associate (1 year, October 2013 – November 2014)

I joined the firm as Vocational Trainee in its assurance department during my second year of university for the periods between February 2014 to July 2013 & June 2011 to August 2011. In October 2013, I took up the offer and joined the firm as audit associate.

Audit Associate

- Assisted in reputable Multinational Companies audit (nature: manufacturing, engineering and electronics,)
- Assisted in two listed companies audit (nature: construction)
- Assisted in US-SOX audit engagements, Agreed-Upon-Procedures engagements and International Reporting.

Vocational Trainee, Audit

 Assisted audit seniors in performing vouching for various sections, assets sighting and stock takes.

QUALIFICATIONS

Bachelor of Accounting Information System (Hons), Universiti Utara Malaysia 2009-2013

- Graduated with Second Class Upper
- Awarded with Dean's List twice

Remarks: Currently pursuing professional qualification – ACCA (Status: Pass: P1 Governance, Risk and Ethics P3 Business)

SKILLS

Languages English (Fluent), Mandarin (Conversational) and Malay

(Conversational)

Dialect Hokkien (Conversational)

IT Proficiency Microsoft Office: Word, Excel & PowerPoint